[music]
Well, my name is Kir and I [singing]
dare put Derp. Oh, [music] won't you
come and derp with me?
>> Oh, welcome to a very special derp with
Gerb. An emergency derp with Gerb. What
with World War II getting started and
actual uh we decide to have a great uh
professor to professor talk. Hold on.
There's
Holy [ __ ] I hate motorcycle people,
dude. I hate I hate them. Anyway,
Professor Jang's on the show. Please
welcome Professor Jiang.
>> Thanks, Kirk.
>> Do you do you have motorcycle pro? Where
are you located?
>> I'm in Beijing. Um and we have a
problem. We have a scooter problem. Not
not a motorcycle problem because
scooters are like rats. So like they're
like everywhere. So if you're just
walking in a park, suddenly like two
scooters converge on you and you get run
over.
>> So [laughter]
>> I went to Beijing.
>> I went to Sujo Hughai.
Oh, Hoa. That's right.
>> Yeah. Hu. [clears throat]
>> Yeah.
>> And uh I can't remember the last one.
>> I did a kung fu comedy tour toy there.
But uh Shanghai that was wild. I I
didn't really see any Chinese stuff the
whole time I was there. It was all like
Shanghai was like the village kind of.
>> Shanghai is Europe, man. You're not
really in China, so it's not. But but
you're you were really in the best part
of China. So So you should come back and
visit Beijing.
We'll go get duck or something, you
know.
>> Oh yeah, I'll get some duck in Beijing
for sure. I only had hot pot. That's the
only Chinese food I had. The rest was ve
very high quality like western food.
That's all that there was on on the
road. They cheated you, you know. They
cheated you. Um,
>> the hot pot times, this is 2014, maybe.
>> Yeah. So, so to eat authentically in
China, you need to eat pig spray, rats,
um, locusts,
um, you know,
>> is this what is this Chinese black m? Is
this goo that where you eat a centipede
out of the bowl that
>> something like that? Yeah. Yeah. But but
yeah,
>> is that a real pengalin? I don't I don't
know. I uh I don't think uh you know I
think we got our own Wuhan virus out of
Raleigh myself. Um but anyway, you
you're a professor. Do you teach at
university or is that just like a a
commercial title? [laughter]
>> Okay.
>> My judgeship between me and you.
>> So uh I'm not really a professor. I mean
like I'm a professor as much as you are
a judge. Right.
>> Nice. So 100% qualified. Yeah.
>> Right. So, so yeah, I teach high school
and I have a BA from Yale and that's the
extent of my um education. Real Douglas
Murray got sick of school. Yeah,
>> I got sick of school. Um yeah,
>> you Murray has a BA bachelor's of
English. [laughter]
>> Yeah, and he knows everything, right?
So, there you go.
>> He's one of the greatest.
>> Hey, so I was wondering if you could do
me a favor. I was hoping you could um
title this episode the multiverse of
madness because I'm a huge fan
>> of of your show and
>> I want to call this a multiverse of
madness
>> because I because like you're insane.
I'm insane and I was hoping that we
could go really into deep insane um
things I couldn't talk about anywhere
else because otherwise um you know they
they would just ban me or something.
[snorts]
Uh, well, I was very strange on YouTube.
I have a warning that's on the top of my
channel that says if you look, if you
try to downplay Ukraine, the Ukraine
situation anyway, they can take just
take my money from the channel.
[laughter]
>> Oh,
>> that's a thing that's written here. I
mean, it's absolutely bad [ __ ]
>> you know. So, I if you notice, we got uh
uh masked like the HBO version of
Watchmen that sucked. We got that deal
now with the uh cops. They just hired
anybody to be a ice cop.
>> Yeah,
>> they're going about it in a way I I
wouldn't have picked out for them to go
about it. And uh then on the other end,
we got to uh what did uh they just
Washington Post the reporter just got
his house raided by uh
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] Cash Dick Tracy Patel that that
hero. I mean what [laughter]
uh it looks like we're uh I don't know
how I feel like we're China without the
good um Montre rail kind of now.
>> So so there's this famous Chinese
dissident Iwwayi weii
you know he he's this famous artist and
he left for Germany like 10 years ago
because you know he thought that China
was this authoritarian
place where you couldn't really practice
free speech.
>> Yeah. Then he was in Germany and he's
like, "Oh my god, it's so much worse in
Germany than in China." Okay.
>> I've never It's so beyond
We covered this on Jimmy's show, a clip
of that Ursula, what's her name?
>> Oh, yeah. W I can't remember her last
name, but she she's doing a rally and
something like we're giving all the rest
of your money to this Ukraine thing and
some guy's protesting her
>> and so cops are carrying him away and
she you're lucky in a lot of countries
you'd be arrested for that as he's being
arrested. Like she's saying it as he's
being ar it's what I mean that's just
the peak of um some kind of magic trick.
How would you make people see a thing in
front of their face? You know,
apparently it's the worst in Britain
because, you know, if you start a
pedophile ring, uh you're protected by
the law, but if you speak out against it
and say that there are certain ethnic
groups that are responsible for these,
uh rings, then uh you are put in jail.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, that's because you should
they look, if you're in the UK, you
should have figured out your king's way
into it. So, that's why they protect it.
>> Yeah.
>> Or the Pakistanis doing it. I'm sure
they are. But inbred, did you say
they're inbred? Well, funny story. You
know who else is inbred and into kids?
Your entire ruling class.
>> Yeah. No, these guys these guys are
subcontractors, right? They're they're
like like you know
>> on the streets. Yeah. [snorts]
>> You know, I've been a [clears throat] a
judge a judge for a long time and I've
seen a lot of cases. Well, I heard of
that years ago. The um uh uh the the
trafficking rings, the groomer gangs or
something they were called.
>> Yeah.
>> It was when I was working for Sasha
Cohen show. So the guy I was talking to,
they kind but they're all upper class
Oxford kids, so they they're like, "Oh
yeah, it's this overblown thing." But
England's a small place, dude. It's not
something like that is is such a um it's
like in America, I feel like you would
hide something like that better. It's
just England, they don't have guns, you
know? They got to rely on wizardry
still. So [laughter]
that there's nothing they can really do
about it, you know? I think they banned
ninja swords even pretty recently by
name.
>> Have you ever read John Kare?
>> Uh maybe. What is it?
>> Oh, John Lare. Uh he he wrote these spy
novels. He was very popular uh in the
day.
like
>> um so so his most famous is um um the
spy who came in from the cold and he
wrote this whole smiley trilogy and and
and you know he was he was MI6 um you
know he uh he went to E10 he he was MI6
and he quit the foreign office was like
35 to write novels but
>> he went to gay Oxford
>> yeah yeah but but but I mean the the
point is that he never really quit right
he was always part of that apparatus
>> and if you read his novels
Like it's it's like the biggest problem
in the Secret Service is homosexuality,
you know, it's it's it's like they're
all gay and you know, which are all
pedophiles as well.
>> Do they have rules where like really has
got none? It's really from what I could
tell have nothing to do with actually
like an orientation which would imply
some kind of mutual, you know,
enjoyment. It's like a weird power
Alexander the Great thing, you know,
like uh can I be AC Ducey and like why
why would uh Barack Obama have to go be
an a crack escort for some gay guy that
Tucker has on? Why would he have had to
do that? Well, that's a thing they do in
those circles. It's an initiation.
>> Yeah.
>> You know, and you like Lef Nikita, like
Obama had to do [laughter] that move.
Uh, and so it's got nothing to do with I
mean if you like, let's say you're gay,
you probably got to pretend you're
straight. Or if you're Pete Booty J, you
got to pretend you're gay for some
reason. Never know.
>> That's that's a great point. Yeah.
>> Whatever you don't like, you got to
sacrifice it, you know, like just do
show that you're in.
>> Hazing is a good hazing.
>> So there's this great comment back in in
the 2020 Democratic primaries where Cy
Booker was up against Pete Page Edge.
And Cy Booker is clearly gay, right?
He's pretending to be straight. doesn't
gay boy the two names [laughter]
>> because he's a creepy Buddha jazz
because he's because he just comes out
as gay he was more popular than Corey
Booker right
>> so Booker is like yeah
>> well Corey Booker is an early like AOC
type of like where they media push of
like here's a non-corrupt
>> we're gonna have some changes around
here and then they're you know they're
all flipping out about that mom dami guy
I still demote people that think that
New York is fallen to socialism.
>> Yeah,
>> they're going to have a Christis co-op.
Maybe, probably not. And uh stronger uh
anti-semitism laws. That's what what's
going to happen from that's all going to
happen.
>> Yeah.
>> But people really buy into this still.
And now
>> my theory, sorry. My theory is that um
you like all these DI guys in the
Democratic party like Obama, AOC,
Booker, Madani, they're all Mai Ultra
maturing candidates or every single one
of them. I I don't know what I don't
know what sort of condition they went
through, but they behave the same way.
>> No. Yeah, they do. They all behave like
George W. Bush went I made a joke that I
thought Dick Cheney used to hunt him and
his brother naked through the woods and
as a stupid joke that but I think that
did happen. I think they like that's
part of it. They do the most dangerous
game as a as as training like the Hilton
sisters had to do it and uh a lot of
wellto-do Mormies at the top you know
involved in defense and um you don't you
know you don't get when you get caught
it's uh uh
you don't get killed but it it's real
gross. You don't want you don't want to
get caught but you do get caught and the
whole thing is to degrade you down. It's
it's like the book Precious but at the
top of society [laughter]
>> they have the same lives. They don't get
enough to eat and they're viciously
molested.
>> Well, you know, if you go back to
history, you know, Sparta, the entire
Spartan society was structured around
the traumatization of children because
what they would do is they would take
these kids, every one of them u away
from their families when they were five
or six, put them in boarding school
where they were just beat up every
single day uh by older kids and then
when they were like 12, they were paired
with this um older guy who's like 30 and
they became lovers. And so this guy
became handler, right? They called him
the Charlie Sheen. It was an actual
position in the
>> Right. Right. So all of Spar society was
structured around this this concept.
>> Oh yeah. Well, look um shame and uh
degragation degradation are like a good
uh safe to keep your secrets safe
[laughter] in, you know, like
>> Yeah. hide hide it with the uh PDF file
activity because nobody wants to look at
that too much unless something's wrong
with them, you know? So, it's just like
a really good uncomfortable I don't know
anybody that wants to go on about that,
but Monarch especially is the one that
that is informing all this that that and
nobody talks about it except my friend
Emma's podcast does. And in uh Kathy
O'Brien's book, it was some Chinese
intel guy first told the the guy that
wrote the forward about this program.
So, well, I'm very curious because I
think it's
um you know, I I I never bought the
thing of they kept saying we might have
to fight China for Taiwan. First of all,
I think we recognize it belongs to China
like officially or they say
strategically ambivalent, but they
recognize it. Secondly,
why does China make our shoes and phones
and viruses for us if there are, you
know, and then that stupid spy balloon
nonsense?
>> Yeah.
>> Which I'm going to say is not a spy
balloon because it was a [ __ ]
balloon. By the way, everybody, you jerk
off. Um, and then they say it's a UFO
later. There's so much nonsense involved
with it that it seems like they're to
get somebody's in on it together. not as
a country but
you know like uh either corporate or
just like uh whatever interests that are
are the nations don't matter and borders
don't matter there's just like really
powerful families let's put it that way
>> exactly
>> Wall Street and party are the best of
friends okay I mean these two groups are
so closely knit and look you just Google
where these uh princlings you know the
sons and daughters of the communist
elite where they went to school and
where they're living now and you
recognize that oh my god it's the same
club like these kids of Wall Street
these kids
>> oh yeah the princlings I
>> they go the same schools man
>> um I hadn't even thought of that I was
trying to remember what they called it
but I was thinking about that because
all the 60s and all the stupid [ __ ]
rebellion they made up they're all the
sons and daughters of the generals
they're all like the princlings
>> the guy from Um,
uh, Crosby from Crosby Stills and Nash.
His real name is like Van Vutenberg
Deutschin. It's something crazy. And
he's like a incredibly important
bloodline if you follow that kind of
horseshit, which uh, these people do.
>> So, the princlings are everywhere,
aren't they?
>> And you look at like the the major
social media influencers of today, guys
like Andrew Tate, guess what? Their
families are CIA, you know?
>> Yeah. I thought they thought to fight
better if there was
>> but most about manipulation really.
Yeah. His dad's a uh
>> chess player
>> chess champion.
>> I don't think people get the extent of
um the infiltration but whatever when I
went to China it was very interesting
because it was like a funhouse mirror of
like the same you know like uh any of
our movies that we have there they once
I saw like uh what's that famous one in
China? Um, it's like a Chinese Rambo. It
came out like not that long ago.
>> Oh, wolf warrior. Wolf warrior.
>> And then and then you could tell it was
big because people were using a term
wolf warrior diplomat. Like that's what
they like Trump saying the Donro
doctrine which it sounds like a like a
WWF.
It's like Austin 316 or like
Hulkcomania. It doesn't sound even like
that that doctrine that probably isn't
valid in a legal sense of any kind.
Yeah. So, so I I was going to say like
how we know that this USChina conflict
is all just a show. It's not real is the
fact that Hollywood has not made a movie
where the where China is the villain.
Right. Think about that. Where you know
in
>> they wanted to but they they had to
switch it to North Korea.
>> Yeah. So and so like you know in Top Gun
Top Gun Maverick the enemy was Iran
right? If you look at Captain Captain
America: Brave New World, the enemy is
[clears throat] Japan, not China. Japan.
So,
>> it is. Oh, yeah. Well, oh, no. Yeah,
obviously because Disney wants to push
their mu I can't believe they would push
like their own a Mulan that nobody in
China would like, which is like a
Chinese thing. That was brilliant on uh
Disney's part.
>> Yeah, they they it
>> that's why when uh what's it called? Um,
the original I love where like Russia
and Cuba invade from the guy made uh
what is it Mark? You remember I'm
blanking out with the Wolverines? The
football team has to fight the commies
that invaded the [ __ ] heartland.
Ah, they remade it with Thor and they
changed the themes of it in the original
one. It's all these like survival type.
>> Yeah. Red Dawn. So Red Dawn was and John
Millius. I love like a like movies from
like a maniac that's got like that much
vision. He's just like he has so much
vision as a maniac. That's why Conan is
so great. It's just such like a of it.
Anyway, uh uh they remake it and they
change it so they're not self-sufficient
anymore. They're um the guy who's in
he's an ex soldier so that's why he can
do it and train them.
>> And then it's like it and it was
intended to be China. I don't know who
like when it something else had to be
going on some trade thing where they had
to hastily go back and CGI North Korean
flags on everything.
>> Yeah.
>> And I North Korea I I got to say I I
never really bought the idea that North
Korea was uh going to invade America at
any point. I don't think that was really
on the table ever.
>> Well, you know, Hollywood is a huge
Chinese money operation.
>> Say that again. Well, Hollywood is a is
a huge Chinese money laundering
operation.
>> I mean, just China that must launder a
lot.
>> Oh, yeah. You're right. You're right.
Everyone. Yes. Exactly.
>> I mean, uh, everybody wants to get in
the movies. And And then I I like uh
Isn't Seagal? That's what he's making
now, right? He's making uh Mongolian
moneyaundering kung fu movies. Have you
seen Stephen Seagal's new movies?
>> I'm not I'm not a movie fan. No.
>> Okay. Well, Steven Seagull you should uh
check out because he's all
>> Is he Putin? I mean,
>> say what?
>> Putin, right?
>> I think Putin got sick of him pretty
quick.
>> Well, well, Putin has good taste then.
Yeah.
>> Well, I don't Mark, my engineer tells me
that Steve is like the old school
conspiracy guy, which I find fascia,
[laughter] but uh I might be wrong about
that. I don't know. Uh, I know that he's
got a [clears throat] reputation for uh
uh, you know, sexual harassment, so he
could very well be CIA. You know, that
he'd be qualified. Um,
>> what were some of the conspiracy
theories that he was into?
>> I don't know, Mark. You told me about
it. I don't know what I don't think uh
>> well some of his early films imply
uh the corruption of government,
international trafficking of drugs. So
it's I mean he's he's partially
responsible for writing some of these
films which made me think maybe he had
some sort of involvement in uh in the
themes and whatnot. But that that was a
lot of movies in the 80s to be fair in
the early 90s.
>> Well, Gary D'Vor got his hands cut off,
right? And he was writing a Panama
movie. The guy made command I think he
wrote Commando with Schwarzenegger and
then his car lost control and then they
found him and his he had no hands. was
right when we went and got Noriega
>> and uh and I mean I believe this I don't
know this is definitely a supposedly but
uh Noriega had had Epstein like video of
our officials with kids right around the
same time as the call boy scandal in the
white house and all that [ __ ] um do you
know okay so if you would go really deep
in this [ __ ] I want to know have you
what do you know about the Lee family
and I think it's li is because that
supposedly is of the east like their
version of I don't know what are uh you
know R13
they like every every uh area get has
its own don't it?
Um, okay. So, I don't know what you're
referring to because Lee is a very
common surname in China. So, so could
you provide some some background?
>> Like the Chinese Illuminati families,
professor, like these
>> original triad families.
>> Yeah. Like uh who would who would be on
the list if we were going to name like
some elite families that we could
>> I don't know about it a lot. I know that
there's part of it, but I've I've never,
you know, beyond uh that thing of goo,
which is uh Austin Osman Spear, the
sigil guy, was into that. And uh so my
my girls over Power Cash, I I hadn't
watched it, but I had this terrible
dream of eating centipedes out of a dish
and like a [laughter]
like a red and gold kind of back and I
was like, "This sucks. Why do I have to
do this?" And I woke up and it it tasted
so bad in my mouth that I thought a
spider went in my mouth or something.
wasn't just like puking in your sleep.
So, it disturbed me for a while, this
dream. I'm like, I bet I ate a bug in my
sleep. Anyway, she tells me about this
guy later that he was into this thing
called uh gu. And you put poisonous [ __ ]
in a dish, you know, a centipede, a
scorpion, whatever, and you close it,
and then whoever's alive, you eat that
one to absorb the strength of it. It's
like some old and uh I think I just
picked it up on Wi-Fi or something, you
know, from sleeping. I don't think I've
done that since past life or anything
like that. But that's uh all the
commonalities I noticed with like a
serpent or a dragon or a lizard that's a
dragon or a I mean it seems to be very
common worldwide that the real important
people came from some sort of a a
dragon. [laughter]
>> Right. Right.
>> Why? Why?
>> Right.
Um, you know, I don't know much about
about this. Um, yeah. So, I mean, I
think you're referring to the fact that
uh, you know, when the British came into
China and start the opium trade was
being facilitated by uh, triads, right?
These um, six societies
>> earlier. Yes. Triads were Yeah. Yeah.
Around around China. and they made a
bundle and they stored their wealth in
um in Britain in
>> the Bank of England and after commerce
revolution they all went to Hong Kong
and today they still control Hong Kong
so it's a triads that control Hong Kong
so all the movies that come out of Hong
Kong are all triad movies like guys like
Jackie Chan are all
>> Jason you mean Jackie Chan's movies were
made by triads like the way Steven Gulls
were made by the mob
>> Oh yeah
>> right yeah like everyone knows this
Yeah. And Jackie Chan is is like mafia
like sorry triad adjacent. You know he's
he's clearly a member of a triad
otherwise you can't you can't get big.
Um yeah. So
>> is a triad like um I mean I'm saying
like the Italian mafia but is it like a
freemason more than that? Like is it
like a there's levels in a secret
society and you got to be you know uh
there's initiate do they do all that
kind of [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean I mean like like you
look at any any of the secret societies,
right? And they're all the same
structure, right? You you have different
layers. You have initiation.
>> Um you have certain esquetologies. Yeah.
I mean, they're all the same.
>> It's like the original secret knowledge
that somebody got early is how to create
like a sales funnel or a [ __ ] There's
just you follow this pattern and you can
create uh I think it's their apotheiois
ritual. All these like wizard people,
that's how they think they they're going
to be immortal.
>> Yeah. And the higher you climb, the
crazier it gets because um the entire
point of these escies is to confuse you
and to force you into loyalty, right?
>> So, you know, you look at Scientology
and it's complete nonsense. But, you
know, if you're if you if you're if
you're to be part of the elite, you
know, the the upper management, then you
have to buy into this nonsense. You have
to brainwash yourself. You basically
have to like clear your mind. [snorts]
>> Well, I think you got to join. There's a
lot of crossover for reasons I don't
understand between Mormons and
Scientologists
and uh the Nation of Islam because
Nation of Islam uses uh Scientology.
He like bought Scientology for the
members of the Nation of Islam which
bizarre but what I realized is these are
all fellow mages. They're all fellow
magi
uh helping each other out and all these
religions especially here in America
they got a left-hand path and that's all
the symbology is. So that like, you
know, if you're a Mormon,
you I know a bunch of Mormons that are
not involved in anything crazy, but I
also know a bunch of conmen close-up
magic [ __ ] like Vegas scumbag
types who all say Joseph Smith's a
prophet and they all do tarot and that
kind of [ __ ] And that's because if
you're in the know, they really admire
him for getting his his stupid magic his
coven protected forever and into this
high government. And they have a
left-hand path as well, the left hand
path of God. It's in J.R. Sweet's uh
book about it. And it all makes sense
now because you could see these these
guys hustles. They all support the
mooneyies and them or why are the
mooneyies connected to it? All of them.
>> So, what do you think accounts for the
success of the Mormons in America? Well,
uh, if you want to be
on a scale of, uh, how out there I would
say, you if you really wanted to be
religious about it, you could say that,
uh, Mc Moroni is the prince of America
because this is a principality and all
these countries have their own princes
of the air and what have you. And some
people would say that that prince of
America is the same one from the witch
trials in Salem that uh Tituba said she
asked or projected. It's a dark man, a
dark sworthy man that anyway that's uh
America's Elena the plume serpent but
the prince of America is uh supposedly
Moroni. But also if you have um enough
hypnosis and enough uh like people want
unbelievable [ __ ] that that you have to
believe in as an act of faith. If you
can make yourself believe it thing that
you that is not true. You have overcome
reality itself.
to it. Like I think flat earth is is
that because it's such a thing of like I
couldn't care less what shape the earth
is and I don't get out would figure in
>> and but there's something about that
that is such like a I'm settling on
this. It's such like an exercising of
your free will,
you know, like there's something to that
and if you can harness that, you could
you do real well. And then also if you
do anything to make a book
>> like Joseph Smith
>> Yeah. Hey, I wanted to ask you um um I I
want to pick your brain about Trump.
>> Where do you think Trump comes from and
how does he fit into the larger secret
society? Um uh
>> I I only heard silly gossip and rumors,
but uh my favorite thing that Dick
Gregory used to say is there's two
Trumps,
>> a blue and a red tie Trump. Now, this is
all silly not Oh, he's one of the first
people Dick Gregory to say Michelle
Obama had a dick, which I'm not
completely sold on, I must say.
[laughter]
She could have had a pants wiener in
that dancing video, but he was on he was
say, you know, he had his Zapruder film,
this comedian that Gregory had all this
and um it really is like when we play
his stuff he said just a second ago till
now. And I try to keep track of the
ties, but I forget which ties. I think
red supposed to be the more aggressive
to Trump, but you know, with Biden, it
was like who the tall Biden and the
short Biden. And I'm still not clear if
that was just a a trick from uh you know
uh trying to place him in a place he
wasn't digitally and so they got his
height wrong which it could have been or
he just had like a Saddam Hussein
double. They all have doubles and like
really good masks. So I this I was told
by somebody that Trump was Jesuit
programmed a long time ago. He's from
one of families
>> and I was like I I didn't want to
believe it. And uh by the way Kathy
O'Brien says no. I asked her on Jimmy
show and uh but I noticed a divide
between the [clears throat] boomer age
monarch people and the uh younger
monarch people. They have a much
different real different opin. It's very
interesting. Um but anyway, he's some
kind of Janice figure right now, I guess
you could say. And uh it's wild watching
them
watching him do the opposite of uh
everything that he was supposed to do. I
mean, literally every I don't I remember
Greenland coming up when before the
election. I remember Venezuelan cocaine.
I've done cocaine, all kinds of cocaine
in my life. And you never heard of
Venezuelan cocaine. It's never been a
thing.
>> Every other country, but Venezuela. Um,
yeah. So that's I mean to go that 180
degrees is like almost stick it in your
right in your face where if you don't if
you don't want [clears throat] to accept
reality now you've given us the right to
do whatever we want to now is how I look
at it.
>> So so my question then is what does
Trump want? Where is he taking America?
Like like how
>> oh the scam can't end so they got to
crash it. He's going to crash it. I mean
won't he might not get it done. I guess
he's just got to get us to World War II
or some [ __ ] right? whatever Albert
Pike's last wishes were. He rebuilt the
Pike statue and we're doing all the
things to make a World War III happen.
And it's stunning. Now, if you pay
anybody that pays even a little bit of
attention to it should should see that.
And it's frightening the level that
people don't, but that shows you how
effective the We're way better than
North Korea at programming people here,
>> right? So, World War II is um is is is
happening, but but also it seems as
though he's starting a civil war as
well, right? You look at what's
happening in Minnesota and all and all
this conflict. Um
>> yeah, that's very strange that they
would do it that incompetently. And
meanwhile, the the problem
>> H-1B visas and all them things, you
know, Trump's in the hotel industry and
the hotel people want to pay less to
their employees. So their job, so the
jobs that literally are the ones that
are causing the problem that are being
taken up, they're fine. Uh not to
mention uh that [ __ ] Only Fans for
some reason, they're allowed to stay.
[laughter]
Uh and then they're going to the street
and asking people for their ID just
randomly on the street with masks on
>> in unmarked Subarus.
>> That is so
>> And the chick that got shot when she
>> Yeah. I was like, "Look, if you could do
something dumb like that, they're going
to execute you because
>> they give them all the rights in the
world to do that, the cops." Okay.
>> Uh but no, I think legally, no, they
don't. They're not supposed to get in
front of your car. So, I'm wrong about
that.
>> Not only that, [clears throat] I've
watched them grabbing people randomly.
>> Yeah.
>> That are citizens. The one that was
funny, the guy looks like Shane Gillis.
>> He's being thrown up against the car. He
has guns that are legal. Everything's
legal. He just pissed off this shorter
guy who's got a mask on. It's crazy. And
somebody's just filming it. Everybody's
got to film it as much as possible.
That's all you could do because uh I
think one side ain't getting, you know,
one side is is not getting what they're
supposed to get on these channels other
than a few, you know, I guess Tucker's
telling the truth about it and uh some
people are telling the truth about it,
but it's it's really out there right
now,
>> right? So, so I I want to talk about
Minnesota, right? Because like let's
look at the events before the Renie Good
shooting where Nick Shirley, right, who
is clearly this Republican operative. He
goes into Minneapolis. He starts making
these videos about how these daycare
centers are actually stealing billions
of dollars from the government in order
to finance uh Democratic elections,
right?
>> And and then LMS makes this viral. So,
it seems coordinated. And then
>> right and then Trump what he does is he
says that we're gonna cut funding for uh
for Minnesota and then he sends in 2,000
ICE agents on January 6 or 7th uh to
round up Somali um refugees and that's
when the renegot shooting happens. So it
seems as though um it almost seems as
though Trump wants to make Minnesota
ground zero for a civil war, right? It
seems like some [ __ ] with Tim Waltz to
me. I mean, that operative kid. So, that
kid is supposed to be like the the good
side Fuentes. He's like the Nick Fuentes
Twinkie that loves the Jews and like the
good alternative Fuentes,
>> right?
>> And uh his first story is this big one,
this uh old-fashioned Mormon front
virgin, we'll call him. [laughter] And
[snorts] uh so so I I don't know, Tim
Wall, this is just like some thugggery
[ __ ] that they were just doing to Trump
before he came in. Um as Oh, Trump has
pardoned one of the people involved in
the scam, by the way, already.
Somebody's already been pardoned in the
scam by Trump. It's already happened,
>> right?
>> Uh so of course there's a a scam going.
Of course there is. What is that? The I
mean that as bad. Go lock up Tim Waltz.
Is anybody going to jail yet? Oh no. Oh,
also, um, it's everywhere. That same
scam in Minnesota is in all the places,
[ __ ] They gave all your money to
[ __ ] Ukraine to lose a war. They're
gonna get they're giving you money. Oh,
we kidnapped the president of Venezuela
so that we can get oil to Israel in time
for uh this Iranian push. And I'm
watching psychopaths talking about the
Iranian protesters which are uh I think
exactly just like the thing in uh
Tianaan Square which I remember being
very shocked to learn was a George Soros
NGO thing and Wikileaks revealed what
really went on with that. And I mean yo
that's like one of them kind of who told
me Jackson Hle with his stupid he's got
a great hair that kid but he showed me
the video. I thought this guy got run
over by a tank all these years in this
picture in the poster. And then he
showed me the actual video. I'm like,
that's weird. Billy Joel didn't say. And
then he showed me the Wikileaks from
2011 when it came out, which I'd never
heard of. And I'm like, what? And I
remember I was like
[laughter]
I was upset. Like it was very upsetting
to me like when I found out Two Girls
One Cup was fake. The same level of
anger and bewilderment.
Anyway, that's what this is. this
they're trying to do the same thing.
It's they all do the same trick
everywhere. BLM had it.
>> Look look it's it's a classic color
revolution playbook in Iran where uh
they have these NOS's who organize
people. They control the information
space. They just brainwash people and
then they bribe certain people to follow
along. They have agents go in as
provocators who who lead who lead uh the
protest and who shoot at cops. They they
killed a lot of cops uh in in Iran. The
thing that they have haven't been able
to do which is crucial is they're not
able to bribe the security services
right so um so in Nepal they just bought
the sec security services just disappear
and let and let these 20- year olds you
know uh run out run a muk so they have
they haven't been able to do that um and
and the other thing that was crucial in
Iran that that changed um the strategy
is that Iran was able to bring down
Starlink right they were able to to jam
Starlink but not only that
>> oh I didn't know that
>> yeah they were able to do that they was
able to jam Starlink because that that's
how how they were able to coordinate um
they were receiving orders from overseas
and they were able to to coordinate uh
these these protests but then Iran with
help from the Russians and possibly the
Chinese they able to to jam Starlink
>> but not only that and this is what
what's crucial is
>> once they once they jam Starlink they
were also able to pinpoint
um Starlink modules so they knew exactly
uh who was organizing these protests. So
now they're able to just round up all
these MSAD assets all across Iran. So
this is a huge huge defeat for the
Israelis in
>> I had no idea they had rounded up the
MSAD. I knew it was a MSAD.
>> Yeah. Uh
>> and that's why Trump is delaying the air
strikes because the idea of color
revolution is you have these protests
spread and then you have the air strikes
in order in order to destroy the morale
of the military, the populace and and
show that the protesters are are winning
and then and then you embed uh
insurgents into Iran to to start
challenge challenging the authorities.
So um I think they sent in some Kurd
insurgents a few days ago and they were
wiped out because Turkey betrayed them.
So, so it's a very complicated situation
right now in
>> Yeah. Right. Oh, that's very
interesting.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, but when this happens,
okay, the next stage in the in the
playbook is false flags, right?
>> Because they're not going to give up.
>> There's been a few already.
>> Well, yeah. Yeah.
>> Israel's done quite a few, I would say,
in a row where I haven't forgot about.
There's a that couple that got shot and
the guy laid down a Palestinian flag.
There's no way that's not some program
manurion candidate guy. Yeah. Yeah. This
this is like outside the the Israeli
embassy, right, in Washington DC.
>> Yes.
>> And and and the couple were Christian
Zionists who were working for the
Israelis. And
>> I thought they were Jewish. I thought
they were they were Jewish. Am I wrong
about that?
>> I thought they were Jewish, but I think
they were Christian Zionist. They were
evangelicals. And they had just gotten
engaged and then they died.
>> Wow. I I hadn't heard they were evangel
I'm gonna check that because that's
>> I think so. I think so. It was put out
there as if they were uh Jew cuz you
know Bandai Beach uh and those are a
bunch of Kabad people which means they
got used as sacrificial lambs for that
>> I think. So
>> Kabad is no uh is kabad. They're not
good.
>> Yeah.
>> And uh yeah. So and and it's it's a uh
you know they accidentally like a Muslim
guy helped some people being shot and
they were or stop the shooter. They were
hoping it was going to be like something
not not that. But they do this all the
time. I mean, all of our school
shootings, I don't believe a single one
anymore. I I honestly there could got to
be one, right? But I I don't wouldn't
know what it is. Almost all of them are
uh planned and it was specifically to
disarm people. Australia gave the guns
up after the first autistic spree
killer. They were like, "Okay, here you
go." I'm guessing because they have
healthcare was why they probably did
that. Uh but that's the goal. And I
thought that was crazy my whole life,
but it is not. That's they say it it's
in tragedy and hope it's in all these
books. You got to disarm them because
the bottom line is you can win. That's
what Red Dawn taught [laughter] us about
North Korea invading.
>> Well, there's certainly a pattern to all
these school shootings, right, where the
the school shooter has has a parent who
is either a psychologist, right, who
works in the field of psychiatry or it's
a subcontractor of some sort government
adjacent. So, so that's a really weird
pattern.
>> Behavior modification therapist.
>> Yeah,
>> that's the Trump ear shooter kid uh with
the hair lip.
>> Yeah.
>> Ain't heard from his parents ever since
that thing and you know they scrub the
house and Cash Patel said nothing to see
here.
>> The crazy Blackstone shooting in New
York where a guy drove from LA to New
York with an AR-15.
I I live in New York 20 years that first
of all, a guy just walking with an AR-15
in New York is one of the craziest. That
never happens in [ __ ] New York. But
this guy drove from LA to do that
because he's mad about CTE in football
from when he played high school football
and goes to Blackstone
on the 33rd floor. By the way, they said
he meant to go to the 32nd, but he
actually went to the 33rd floor.
>> Oh, by the way, that woman that got shot
uh that hit the gas and the guy popped
her and uh it was 33rd Street. That's
the street.
>> Wow.
>> Come on, man.
>> Yeah.
>> What is this? [laughter]
you know, like why to throw it out there
that much where I have to like notice it
is is astonishing to me. Like I'm like,
are they really like is something been
uh sped up or and it's hasty now?
Because it,
>> you know, they used to let these
marinate before they hit you with
another.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You you know, you know, I
have to say like, you know, the Charter
Cook shooting, it seemed like 911, but
like a really bad sequel to 911, right?
It had all the all the like um
components of 911 and wanted to turn it
into like this major national spectacle,
but they were like lazy and competent
about it.
>> Well, he was try Yeah. Well, I think um
like I said, I didn't give that guy
enough credit because uh
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Uh bottom line is he must have been
sincerely figuring some [ __ ] out was why
would they kill him?
>> Yeah. So, you know, I never had that. I
don't really have anything hanging over
me like that [clears throat]
as a clown for a living. Uh, but uh it's
what I'm fascinated by now is the amount
of um the reason I believe the crazier
maybe sounding things now is because the
effort to make me not able to listen to
it is so so much. you know,
um the that Fort uh uh Hawkua that
Candace Owens said that that uh what's
their head went to, Erica Kerp went to
for for that to be such a big deal for a
minute in the news is really crazy. And
that's an MK Ultra base, by the way,
Fort Waka, and uh Candace just blasted a
bunch of more information about it
today. And I watched certain people get
real upset about her mentioning that
base. It didn't make any sense to me cuz
like who what did she smear a good base?
Who gives a [ __ ] Uh so there's
something there. I don't understand. I
would like to figure out how John Mappen
because that's who introduced I thought
Erica Kirk to Charlie Kirk in Israel and
that's who her benefactor is. Candace is
is John Mappen. He's Scientologist
Elizabeth Castle and uh he was mad and
I'm with him on this point. Let me just
be fair to John Mappen. They're telling
him he has to house illegal immigrants
in his castle. England was. And he was
like, "Why do I have to do that?" And
uh, you know, we had a whole
revolutionary war over [ __ ] like that.
So, I get John Matin's feelings on it.
But also, he's weirdly into King Arthur
and weird [ __ ] And also, Scientology is
goddamn
Mooneyism for the way they like, are all
these people controlled? I I just wait
to hear when I can hear they're lying.
That's all I'm listening for. You can
say whatever you want to me and you can
lie, but I want to hear I want to hear
all your data so I can compare it, you
know.
>> No, it's really interesting how this
entire narrative it just blow blow blow
up in their face, right? Because like
you remember like after Charlie Cook
shooting, the Pentagon had all these
commercials ready to recruit um you know
Americans who joined the military to
fight these wars to avenge Charlie Kirk
and they had to pull it back because
people were outraged and now like this
Erica Kirk uh tour it's blown up in
their face. You know, there was there
was this um recent town hall between
Barry Weiss and Erica Kirk and it was
fantastic.
>> It was
you didn't think it was a good uh town
hall. [laughter]
>> I mean I mean like the fact that they
have to now to use like Barry Weiss.
Okay.
>> Wow.
>> Incompetent shield, right? She's just
dumb. Um
>> I'll give her a mirror mid level, you
know? I know. I' I've met her. She's
very nice. I'm not I'm I have I'm I'm
astonished the amount of money that
would go into making her in charge.
>> Almost like there's no way she's in
charge and someone else is in charge is
how it looks to me.
>> Right. So so so so I think it's a level
of desperation in that they have to use
Barry Weiss whoever who everyone thinks
is incompetent. I mean and right now
there at CBS News there's just this
revolt a revolt against her. the fact
that Larry Ellison who for like decades
had could hide behind the shadows,
right? Um, and now he has to like show
up and actually to control it. It just
shows like like the narrative is falling
apart, but at the same time it shows us
there's a script in place and they have
to follow the script to to its end. Even
even though like they know that it's a
bomb in the box office when when
actually you know um
>> Yeah, that's a good way. That's a good
way.
>> Just get the production done, move on to
the next film.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, they just giving up, but you know,
there's a script in place. They've been
paid and now they have to have to go
finish it. I mean, it's it's like the
last season of Game of Thrones. They
know it's going to be disaster and it
became so indifferent that you remember
like the last scene of Game of Thrones,
there's a Starbucks. Yeah,
>> there's a [laughter] Starbucks in the
scene.
>> You are like Starbucks cups of the
production. [laughter]
>> We don't care anymore, you know.
>> Yeah, right.
like they were on to bigger and better
things those guys and they didn't want
they I that was amazing to watch like
where
>> you know uh I blame uh what's his name
for not finishing the goddamn books
because obviously these two would not
have been able to uh like replicate his
writing style like you know you kind of
need the guy you can't just go off notes
is what we learned from that. Yeah, but
but but I mean like like George Martin
has set it up so it couldn't be
finished. I mean like like I mean like
>> it it can't be finished. Like I I've
read all his books and he and like the
way the plot is set up is like you just
can't end it because it just meanders
everywhere and it's supposed to be like
this open-ended world like it's it's
almost like World of Warcraft MMOs where
[snorts] it's supposed to openended like
like world onto it onto itself and
that's the appeal of it. But it just
means like there can't be an ending
because there's no logical end point to
to this world.
>> Well, [snorts] he's basing off so much
history and now the creepy [ __ ] with
dragons might he might be based on some
real [ __ ] with that. So in real life it
hasn't [laughter] he would have an
ending for now. So how would he wouldn't
have one yet? He really is like uh like
the uh you know the day of rest god all
fat with a sea captain hat on not
finishing the book. That's what he
that's what he represents to me.
>> So So I I have a theory about guys like
George Martin and Donald Trump. Okay. Um
>> you know even if they don't they
understand the Cabala they do have an
intuitive understanding of the Cabala.
So what's the Cabala? The Cabala is the
understanding that mind over matter
right it's a mind that is the universe.
The universe is conscious. And so the
guys like Trump and guys like Martin,
their understanding is if I can
concentrate people's attention to a
point and that and I think by that point
like if they're all focused on me
>> Yeah.
>> then I don't have to die, right? I can
live on forever because
um
because if you capture enough attention
and you're in consciousness of everyone
then you're the conversion point of
reality
>> and so you can be God. Right. So
>> the Mormon teach it the Mormonism
teacher. You'll be your own god and
you'll have your own universe around
you.
>> Right. Right.
>> Yeah.
>> As long as you can capture everyone's
attention, you know. And like and like
before this wasn't before this wasn't
possible but now we with the advent of
film of media of the internet right you
can like literally capture everyone's
attention and focus their attention
specifically on you
>> so that you can live forever you look at
a guy like Trump right so um like you
know Michael Wolf Michael Wolf has
written many books about Trump so you
know he's like this Trump whisperer he
spent he spent a lot of time with Trump
>> that guy yes
>> oh he's in the Epstein files trying to
work to get it
>> he's like Epstein's PR agent, right?
They were talking about how to screw
over Trump, right? So, so it's a pretty
nasty world,
>> but you know what what what EP what um
Michael Wolf said is that he's talked to
Donald Trump and he asked Donald Trump
like what is your ambition? What do you
want from life? And Donald Trump is like
basically I want to be the most famous
person in the world like and he said it
at to me like I I want to be more famous
than Jesus, right?
>> And so like what does it get you? Well,
in Trump's uh worldview, it gives you
immortality because if people all like
are focused on you, if people are paying
attention to you, and it doesn't matter
if it's good attention or bad attention,
if people are focused on you, then um
you are reality itself. So, so, so, so I
think that's that's the intention here.
Well, maybe I look, like I said, I I
know he's an honorary
33rd degree, some horseshit. And uh they
all are into that [ __ ] They're they're
all in. And also, it's called the Enigma
of uh something his title. It has Enigma
in it. Remember that that little letter
where it was like Ennigmas never age.
You ever noticed that, Jeffrey? Where
they're going back and forth? That
little weird uh page from a book. It had
like a play in it. It was very strange
when that first came out, but it's
called the enigmatic uh something degree
of something. It's gay. I don't know. Uh
famous people get Oh, paranoid American
who was here uh uh two episodes ago was
explaining it like Kramer from
>> Seinfeld
>> got it pre not for the incident. that
wasn't his final initiation saying the
n-word at the uh but but they the fame
is a big part of that and um I mean
that's what the whole promise of the you
know the stars you're a Hollywood star
that's like a Lucifer that you get to be
a Lucifer you know you shine everybody
looks at you and people feel like they
don't exist unless you look at them like
how Adam ain't there unless you look at
it that's how people feel they literally
don't exist until you know that's why
the the need for a god or the feeling of
that is because if you're not being
measured then what are you? You're
nothing. You have to have something to
differentiate you from other [ __ ] you
know, or or there's nothing.
>> Yeah. And and you know, I mean like and
so that's why George Martin can't finish
a book because the point the point at
which he finishes the book is the point
he dies because then people are are
released from this tension, right?
People are
>> [laughter]
>> No, no, I'm serious. I'm serious.
>> You might be right, dude. Wait a Hold
on. That's funny [ __ ] It might be
right. He's doing a Dorian Gray with
this.
>> Yes. [laughter]
>> Yeah.
What do people think about when they
think about George B? They think about
like when is he going to finish a damn
book, right?
>> He can't die until Oh my god.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> He's doing the same trick as that uh PDF
file who made Jeepers Creepers.
>> Yeah. He'll never tell you what that
creeper is because he knows you're going
to throw his throw him away when you
find the spoilers.
>> Exactly. Exactly. And you know what? You
know what? I bet you he's right.
>> I bet you he lives for a long long time.
Even though like like he is in the worst
possible shape, okay, for a human being.
>> Yeah. He's not a
>> No,
>> he's not a healthy he's not like a
acrobatic Samo Hung kind of chunky guy.
He's in a I've seen him up close. I was
like, "Why are you just acting like you
got all this time to finish the book?
You don't." And that was 10 years ago,
probably at the Emmys.
>> Yeah.
>> You [laughter] know what? He looked like
he was going to die when I saw him at
the Emmys. And it's been years since
then.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. He's figured it out, man. He's
figured it out.
>> Ah, that's a good uh Oh my god, that's a
great uh scheme. I didn't even think of
that. But yeah, I guess it all works off
the same thing. you're just focusing on
your attention and making it adds
density to an object, you know. That's
why uh I was always in trouble. That's
why like, you [snorts] know, uh when
Harry Potter first came out and it was
being burned by like church groups were
were burning it because of witchcraft
book, you know.
>> Right. Right. Right.
>> And then later trans I guess witches
were burning it because she didn't
support trans. It went full circle from
conservative to the super left, fake
left of uh hating her thing. But but uh
she created a thing like that. She like
I I put the blame squarely on JK Rowling
for that because you you
>> created your magical world of [ __ ]
transform wmy potions and uh you know
maybe get a man to help you next time
instead of your female imbalance. And
now what happens? Bunch of fruity dudes
with tits and dicks are coming after
you.
Get a man to help you, [ __ ] No,
[laughter]
wait. Let me just check. Uh because I
bet people have uh questions and [ __ ]
and I should check it out, but uh we'll
do a couple right now.
>> Okay.
>> Um okay, let's see. Steve Oh, thanks,
Steve Bertram. This is the most
simultaneously excited and worried I've
ever been about a podcast episode
because of probably audio troubles. Me
too, man. Pecking derp. [laughter]
Uh, exopath call good call in the funny
outfits. My wife voluntary chose your
episode to watch and subsequently got
red pill to oblivion. Cheers from Mount
Chasta. Listen, stay out of that
mountain. And two, uh, why is big guy
why has always got to be a pill? Is
everybody disturbed by that language?
All the is big farmer that much in
control that everything is learning is a
[ __ ] color of pill that Hunters
Thompson is a [ __ ] warlock I think.
All right. Richard Adams 9587. Do
Chinese high school students have a
romantic view of America or do they want
to stay in China?
>> I I'll answer this. Yeah, absolutely. Uh
it's amazing. It's it's like disturbing
how much in love Chinese are with
America. You know, like in America, like
the the the the American dream is to be
able to go to Starbucks one day and
drink a latte. That literally is the
Chinese dream. If you're a peasant uh in
uh China and you have nothing, you want
to work hard, you want to get in
university so that one day you can go to
Starbucks or McDonald's or Dunkin Donuts
or, you know, whatever. Okay, that's
>> not the culture.
>> Not in the cities. In the rural parts,
the cities had all that [ __ ] when I went
there.
But even those cities, you just want to
go to America, man. You know, you want
to go to America and and go watch a LA
Lakers game and
>> you know, like like like like that's
like like like American
like culture is considered like high
class in China. That's the level
brainwashing in uh in China. [snorts]
Well, I mean stuff uh [laughter] you
know what's really funny is when they're
trying to sell movies in China, which
they could have done very easily, but
they just would not accept that Chinese
are not the same as [ __ ] ABCs,
American Chinese or just American Asian
with all that horshit corporate
sensitivities.
>> They don't want DEI. They hate DEI. They
want white. Okay. Seriously.
>> Yeah. No, I saw the better.
>> What? I saw a show of a guy. It was just
a white dad taking care of a blonde
baby. Like a chubby white dad and a
chubby blonde baby. And it instead of a
laugh track, it was women old Chinese.
Oh, that was the show.
>> It was very popular show. Okay. Wait.
>> Uh Ker Ukraine. That is uh I believe
that's how you pronounce it. Yeah.
>> Uh from hemorrhoid Herz. Uh way faster.
I wanted for my birthday. I said uh a
geer counter. She says stop watching
that ker. Uh, oh, the C-word, the the
British aloha, we'll call it. And don't
super chat what I just [laughter] said.
Could you ask Jen a question in
[laughter] Me Love if there's time? Hold
on. Let me get through. Uh, I saw a
behavior panel and they assess Erica
Kirk. Apparently, she's 100% honest. Are
they part of the thing? Um, I don't
know. I have to watch it myself. 100%
>> all these are like paid and and and and
bought for like
>> well Scott Rouse is a good uh uh I like
talking to Scott Rouse because he's a
good uh he's usually the one I would
agree with most of all the body language
people but um
I mean Erica
you know also Scott when I asked him
about Cash Patel it's like he didn't
look it didn't look good.
Um, let's see.
What do you think about the William
Sasha Riley interview? What's that? I
don't know what that is. William Sasha
Riley. Love from Canada. Keep it up. Uh,
uh, dear Capernicus, I think you and
Jenna uh, made Chase change their swazy.
[laughter]
You know, Chase Bank has a swastika,
Professor J.
>> No.
>> The the the uh, symbol of Chase Bank is
a swastika,
>> right? It's like a, you know, it's in a
very old symbol. It's, you know, it
looks like the process charge swaza.
[snorts] A good friend of mine was
invited to, uh, Dew headquarters in the
early 90s due to him being involved in a
program to sell cars to college
students. He took pictures of massive
underwater bases being constructed in
the dry docks.
What? Send them over, dude. I'd like to
see those pictures. I think it's cool.
>> Also, I'll point out that um, the South
Koreans are crazy. So, so you may have
heard that uh in South Korea a fairy was
capsized like maybe 10 years ago, right?
So, there's this fairy that capsized. It
was all
>> Yeah.
>> apparently. Okay. It's a ritual
sacrifice because you know like like the
the South Koreans just take whatever is
American and they make it like crazy.
Okay.
>> So, so the the Christianity in um in
South Korea it's all cult. It it's it's
very cultish. CIA created they find wack
jobs and fun them.
>> Yeah. So that's so so that that that
very capsizing it it was a ritual
sacrifice. They just killed 20 school
children.
>> They're all school kids. Who is that?
>> Oh yeah.
>> And who's the woman in power and Korea?
South Korea got upset about this. Didn't
it cause like a a riot or almost a It
caused a problem that ferry incident?
>> Yeah. No, it's a huge scandal there.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's it's very Belgian of them. Uh
I was never molested. I was too ugly for
Satanist. I don't say that, you know.
Try look smacking they call it. Uh when
did you decide to teach narcissism and a
detachment from physical gain in the
form of game theory? Was it your time as
Princeton? Well, is this is this
Professor Jen because I wasn't at
>> I was never at Princeton. I I was at
Yale.
>> I hate game theory. Oh, you were at
Yale. Did you see any which uh besides
Skull and Bones? They got all kinds of
they got Slytherin House and uh
>> Yeah. No, they have 12. They they have a
lot of secret societies and and besides
secret societies, there are like all
these like clubs as well called the like
there's like the Elizabeth club. So like
Yale it's just like this nexus of all
like these different groups, right? But
but I was a reject. No one liked me, you
know? Uh
>> really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I was I I was a loner at
at Yale. Yeah. So
>> you think they charge you for further
impro implanting and and programming?
>> Yeah, you would think so. You would
think so.
>> For a loader. Hey.
>> Yeah. But but but you know like like
like I think that that what they're
really good at, especially these
professors at Yale, right? Because like
they're all CIA, but what they're really
good at is figuring out what your limits
are. And um
>> right,
>> they didn't they you know, I mean like
like I didn't pass a test. Um I'm I'm
sure there are like series of series of
tests that they look for.
>> Yeah.
>> Um uh you know like these check
checklists and I didn't fit the bill,
you know. I I was a loner. Um I was very
sensitive, but there was something about
me that turned them off. So
>> um yeah. Well, I bet that's how it works
with UFO contact as well. I think they
just the way the Hell's Angels will go
through your whole your background like
you join the Secret Service. I I imagine
this phenomena does that as well. And
you only want you want the least hassles
possible. You want the ones that are the
most
>> Yeah.
>> You know, likely uh predictively
programmed. They don't need everybody to
go. Oh, hold on. This may be important.
>> Um yeah, wait, wait, hold on. I'm
getting com What? Wait up. Mark, what's
up?
>> Sorry. I'll get better at not
interrupting you in the middle of a
sentence. Uh, but you were saying
something if you want to finish your
sentence before I ask.
>> Well, you remind it's it's right in line
with what I was going to ask. But, uh,
Professor Jen, I was wondering uh, to
what degree do people in China and maybe
other Asian countries as well believe in
UFOs and this sort of thing? Uh, because
the disclosure movement, as you probably
know, is pretty popular here over the
past couple years. UAP sightings. Is
this kind of thing talked about in
Chinese media at all or in the public?
>> Look, the reality is that in China,
people believe what the government tells
them to believe. Um, they're, you know,
for I mean like like Chinese have been
conditioned to be the most compliant
people on earth. So their imagination, I
mean, doesn't really exist, but their
imagin imagination is framed or
constrained by the dictates of the
government. Um so there isn't this UFO
all culture there isn't um you know much
religion in this country basically um
there isn't much logic in this country
as well. So when you engage in a debate
with a Chinese, it's not really a
debate. It's more like, you know, like
my father is this government official
and therefore I'm right. And then No,
no, that that that's
>> I remember them explaining it to me. But
what's funny is um like if you know the
rules and they don't change constantly
it could be kind of reasonable you know
in some way cuz like you know when I was
there they go I'm doing a standup show
and I technically wasn't supposed to but
they were like they they they were cool
with everybody they had to be cool with
to run these shows um and uh somebody
had said they were spreading
anti-communist propaganda like a bar
that was jealous because standup was
pretty popular. So the officials were
like, "We know that you're not doing
that, but like somebody reported, so we
have to say you can't do it for a month,
which means like we can't catch you
doing it for a month."
>> Right. Right.
>> You know, and and so uh uh like that
kind of like a level of corruption where
you you know like where you stand. What
we had what we started doing here,
especially there like that you can't
they told me don't say anything about
the Chinese government. Talk about
whatever except that. Okay. And I didn't
know anything. So fine. Uh, you know
what you could say and not say to have a
problem with like the interior ministry,
whatever professionals enforce that.
What they did here was this private
[ __ ] contracted self-made militias of
blue hairs that went around doing their
own little version of the Chinese uh
culture, the culture revolution,
>> but a shittier privatized version of
weaponized gender blob people. And it it
was horrendous. And they were counting
on that, by the way, to make all these
other things. Okay, now that how
annoying that was. And it was very
annoying. But they clearly are not the
ones in power now, [ __ ] So you you
can't keep pushing woke on me as my
enemy cuz I don't have to respect them
at all. I'm worried about the masked,
[laughter]
you know, masked people grabbing you off
the street and asking what the [ __ ] is
that? That's not how you're supposed to
do that.
>> Yeah. I mean, like, you know, and I the
artist who just came back to China, he
says the same thing where, you know, in
China, you know where the lines are. you
know, if you don't piss off the
government, you know, if you stay w
within your place in society, you're
fine. You can say whatever you want. No
one cares. But um you know, Germany,
Britain, United States, these are like
real honest to God totitarian nations
that demand, you know, that you think a
certain way and speak a certain way and
that and that's the priority, right?
Like
>> we got to compete with China. That's why
that's [laughter] what they say.
>> No, no, no. KIND OF
>> CATCH UP TO CHINA CENSORSHIP. They're
all saying it now.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no. China's not like
this. Okay, I'm I'm telling you.
>> No, I know.
>> There was more freedom 100%. By the way,
>> Oh, yeah.
>> You overall now you know the test of
though it would be like the next COVID
if we if Trump wasn't in and was the
other it was the the Wendy Williams
[ __ ] We'd have a bird flu [ __ ]
pandemic right now.
>> Yeah. I have friends that still wear
masks to this day and for whatever
reason and in China when I went I go
this looks like the future and it was
the future. Some people just always wore
masks. [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> It was amaz It was like going to
Bladeunner.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, that's you know
that that that's exactly what's going to
happen in China where if the economy
tanks they will declare like a virus and
everyone's just stuck at home for the
next 5 10 years. Um that that that's
China's future. Like I'm I'm not I'm not
even joking here. Like
>> it seems like a worldwide phenomena that
was Russia got planned that is anybody
allowed to go anywhere or do anything in
the upcoming future of any of these
countries. I've never seen such a push
to get us. So we're going to have AI
suck up all the power.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. That and I don't think the AI
work as well. I think they like I think
they're behind China's AI too, honestly.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Look look look look Kurt
I I'll tell you this. Okay. So my theory
is this. So you know there's a deepseek
phenomenon a year ago right where you
know open AAI had chatbt and then uh
deepseek in China just says you know we
have a better algorithm that's cheaper
that costs like you know like you know
1% or 01% of the cost of your open AI
model and it became a huge huge news
story. Well here's my theory. So if you
talk to like a computer scientist what
what the computer scientist will tell
you is that in order to create this
model what you first need to do is
scrape the entire internet okay which
which is what open AI did and that's why
it was so expensive like figure out
every piece of information on the
internet okay but once you have all this
information then what you can do is you
you can actually optimize the algorithm
figure out a shorter path to get all
this information that's what deepseek
did so so what happened was that open
AAI spent these bills of dollars to
create open to create chbt and then what
openai did was just give everything to
deepsee which then can optimize the
algorithm and and seem as though China
superior and why would they want to do
that to create this threat of AI from
China and it's like now that's why we
have to spend $200 on data centers in
America because otherwise the Chinese
will destroy us right
>> I mean wouldn't they do that by the same
people really and like deep and open
it's you go behind the scenes behind the
curtain it's the same people man
>> well you That's 100% true. Do do you
remember when um uh Mark Zuckerberg
named his baby after Xi Jinping
[laughter] and Xing like don't do that.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> He was creeped out by it. [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's very strange. I just am
watching them uh every new clip and like
only a few people Well, Jimmy plays him
on his show luckily, but uh it, you
know, even if somebody's like, "Hey,
these Muslims are crazy. People, they
want to get a good Muslim,
you know, the old hates of of two of uh
911's going and um you know, I remember
all that. I remember being like, "Oh, if
you draw their profit, they lose their
[ __ ] and they'll kill you." I remember
being thinking they were big babies. And
then uh but here's what I don't
remember. They never had a big
culture-wide argument about if women
have [ __ ] or not, you know. So, point
point to the Muslims on that one. They
they were way ahead of us on that. They
didn't lose the scientific knowledge of
if women have dicks or vaginas.
I can't believe anybody thinks anything
sounds crazy after the last 12 years of
that [ __ ] And by the way, that's what
when we stopped talking about North
Korea getting nukes because we had to
have Seth Rogan go kill the guy in the
movie [laughter] because if they get
nukes, oh, and then they got nukes and
nothing came of it again and it was
nothing but gender [ __ ] for like 12
years.
>> Listen, like I listen to you a lot and
you make this great point where they had
to do this crap because um Occupy Wall
Street really freaked them out, right?
>> Yeah. like uh I mean they they were
scared of a class war and that's why he
had had like to swift um switch towards
DEI and all this wolf crap
>> right
>> good old Miami Obama really uh oh I
think he made it possible to have these
mass police too by the way I think the
reason we have it because he set that up
with the uh well whatever we don't have
I don't even know what habius corpus
means the words but they could just grab
you for whatever reason now
>> just it's pretty much the same as
anything you've ever heard of
>> and it's so scary Yeah, it's so
>> Yeah, I I I would have thought that. You
know what I didn't realize is um because
they don't have to kill you just for
telling the truth about this [ __ ]
You're not going to live that long
anyway. And and these are generational
projects like a pyramid like
>> exactly
>> you know like Rogan
[clears throat] they're getting mad at
him now for because he said and and he
don't get credit for this like he should
get when he was telling people to get
off the left and right [ __ ] cuz
that's not a thing no more. You could
tell who's no [ __ ] good because they
jumped on him for it. Um Um but guess
what? They got 30 Proto Rogans ready to
go that they're gonna and yeah, if you
like the show like that's not the same
thing. But guess what? It only takes a
couple generations to forget every other
[ __ ] thing. Everything's based on
erasing the past quicker than ever
before. Never mind forgetting your
Atlantis history. You don't You're
supposed to forget like a month ago,
dude. Nobody remembers [ __ ] from a month
ago.
>> Look, look, I I'm Look, you look at
World War II, okay? How much of World
War II that we've been taught in school
do you think actually happened during
World War II? You know, like our
understanding of World War II, do you
think that that's actually what
happened? I I don't know.
>> Well, I you could do certain things by
by the propaganda of the winners, for
sure. I I always thought, you know, that
I know Hitler's the new Satan of the
century. Like our new secular Satan is
kind of old of a secular Satan, but uh
that's set up by Wall Street. Like the
the fact that Wall Street directly
created,
>> they propped up all these people now and
Stalin and I mean Lenin,
>> they propped them all up. It's all these
rich [ __ ] paid for this
>> gain of function research. Which one's
going to take over? use a control
>> like and you go back to Marx okay Markx
was a I mean he's no different from like
Nick Fuentes of today where at that time
in history in the 1850s social democracy
socialism was huge around the world
right
>> and communism what it did was it sort of
um invalidated or made socialism look
like an extreme radical
um religion that had
>> yeah dude that's a good point yep
it's it really is cheap trick of um
taking a thing that most people would
agree with and turning it into something
that means the opp you know like that's
that's real real magic work right there.
That's what
>> it always works. I mean it's it's really
simple what they do and it always works.
>> Well, I don't know why I stopped working
on me and and a because I'm that smart.
I it took me quite a long time if I
think about people that told me and
stuff that I could have looked at but I
would not look at. Okay. I just wouldn't
look at it. So, I feel like it took me
quite a long time to notice a lot of
[ __ ] Um, and and uh I'm shocked that,
you know, like I did Julian Doyy's
podcast. He said I predicted they're
going to grab the guy from Venez which I
did not predict, by the way. It's just
covering news that but it doesn't get
covered. So, almost nobody knows any of
the [ __ ] news. So you look like
you're a [ __ ] prophet because you
read like you happen to get actual
information for once that I mean what a
great uh system man you can keep people
behind. That's probably like real time
travel just pushing you down and then I
just uh get all the info and all the
advanced uh tech and I'll be like a
future god and you know and and I could
change the calendar to what I want. It's
I got big plans when I'm done with this
podcast. I went,
>> what was your what was your turning
point? Like at what point did you say,
you know what,
>> when I forgot if we were still in Iraq
in in like uh I don't know, I was on
Facebook
>> fighting with like a [ __ ] feminist or
some [ __ ] Something stupid as something
dumb, dude. And uh then I was like,
"Hey, we still in Iraq at I don't
remember why even it came up, but it
felt like a leaving the oven on
feeling." And I had to look up if we
were still there. I had to look up like
whatever happened with that war. It was
so disturbing of a feeling to be like,
"Oh yeah, didn't we have like a war
going for like the last and it just went
for a while so I don't think about it
and then it just went down like what the
[ __ ] is that?" And so that's the
beginning. And then uh you know as
[snorts] [ __ ] got as the the Occupy Wall
Street as that ESG Black Rockck [ __ ] got
pushed down as the fake left in America,
it got worse and worse. Especially if
you're funny. the economy as bad as it
was was like a little like a little
better because people were there were
still enough people with the luxury of
whining about [ __ ] You know,
previously before the the social justice
movement, they had a term called first
world problems that they'd say if you
whin about something with your feelings,
they go first world problems. That was
the liberal thing to say. And nobody was
saying that no more about first world
problems. I couldn't believe it. And
then it just they all went with the
trend and it just has stayed like that.
And now it really depends
like all my friends that did well
there's a lot of my friends that did
well you know I know a bunch of people
in comedy you can it's unusual for them
to know anything
>> if they're successful and that's like a
lot of people but the bottom line is we
don't have enough middle class to do
that no more. So the beauty of America
is you don't have to give a [ __ ] about
nothing till it happens to you. And
guess what [ __ ] is going to happen
to you. So you don't have to believe
nothing I say. [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> The time will tell you.
>> Look look all these ICE tactics. I mean
it was pioneered and refined overseas,
right? So like
Iraq, you know, you know, occupations,
what's happening in Gaza? I mean like
they've got there's tons of data points
that that that they can now use to
control American uh population. They
know exactly how to instigate a civil
war, right? Um so so so so like I I go
on podcast and I I'm predicting a civil
war and everyone's like, "Well,
Americans are too complacent to start a
civil war, right?" Well, yeah, I I
understand that Americans don't want to
start the civil war, but the deep state
wants to start a civil war,
>> right? and and and they got this
playbook that they refined in everywhere
around the world and they know exactly
what buttons what buttons to push, how
to control the media landscape, how to
infiltrate groups. I mean like like like
it's it's a pretty sophisticated
playbook that they have.
>> It's an ancient play. I mean oh yeah the
clock's ticking the Here's the thing.
The house of cards of lies that they got
going that's crumbling. So that's why
there to me there's a scram. If I
figured any of this out by now then that
means it's not going well. if I if I
pieced any of it together. Trust me.
[laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. And so now there's a mad dash to
follow the script. Um um Richard Grove,
I can't recommend his channel enough.
Grand Theft World. And that's the guy
that really put me on to a lot of [ __ ]
was was Richard Grove. He said, "You
can't stop that scam. There's only one
outcome for the scam is you got to crash
it. So what gets us out of the scam?"
Well, traditionally a big war, you know,
a civil or a uh a world war is how you
typically get out of the the bubble
created by the scam [laughter] and uh
gibberish about the fourth turning. Have
you heard of the fourth turning?
>> Yeah.
>> And uh and like it didn't used to be
like that. Oh, these small cycles. These
are all post World War II. They're not
like
>> Yeah.
>> ancient Mayan calendar [ __ ] They're
they're these [ __ ] planned this. And
the creepiest uh uh is uh Mark gave me a
book when I was playing Saratoga Springs
uh was a big new Brzinski's book about
the technocracy
uh you know Morning Micah from uh
Morning Joe.
>> Yeah.
>> Who was a trilateral creep who helped
install the Ayatollah that we hate so
much. Those guys Rockefeller and and him
they're like no let's put the ayatollah
in now. Uh but he goes in the techn okay
in the technocratic society
uh let's see he sees as the new order of
society coming into ascendance after
Marxism the trend would seem to be
towards aggregation of individual
support of millions of uncoordinated
citizens easily within the reach of
magnetic and attractive personalities
effectively exploiting the latest
communication techniques to manipulate
emotion and control reason. That's the
world of influencers written about in
the 70s.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Oh, I guess they did their thing. It's
happening.
>> Yeah.
>> That's what certain magnetic
personalities will mobilize whatever and
then they'll control the knobs or who
gets reach and uh it it's really
something you could it's starting to
really take shape what the plan is like
uh uh how how it'll be governed.
>> Well, and also you have AI, right? So
like why are they building like these
trund trillions of dollars of these data
centers all around America? Like for
what purpose? It just so that you can
cheat in school just so you can create
these like these silly like uh videos
just so you can have an AI girlfriend.
No, like the purpose is to be able to
monitor you uh to monitor every facet of
your life, right? Digital currency,
digital ID. That that's a game plan.
>> Oh, you know, it's not to power my my uh
digital girlfriend. That's what I had to
see. [clears throat]
>> No, you have
girlfriend and you'll love her to death.
>> Yeah.
>> And she should be the best thing that
ever happened to you. Okay. But
>> my AI girlfriend is going to need a lot
of power. I'm going to tell you that.
Right. [laughter]
>> I don't like 3D women. Have you ever
seen the derogatory terms for 3D women
by people that are into that? I'm
forgetting that.
>> What is that?
>> You know, like all that VTuber [ __ ]
>> you know. Listen, China is right to
mistrust Japan. Let's let's face facts
with that. Uh [laughter] that that
really anime has destroyed
a generation that and school shooter
pills and colorful anime. It does
something turns a white man into a white
woman and a black man into a white man.
All right, let's see. Ask him his take
on the Google trend data he found.
Minneapolis uh ice shooter showed up two
days before the event. Oh, no way.
So, you know how before the shooting,
uh, the searches go up on these people
for Charlie? Well, on Jimmy Door Show, I
go, "Hey, someone should look up for all
the shootings."
>> And then they did and sent it to me. And
it turns out it's all of them.
>> It's all of the shootings going back to
the Virginia Tech.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So, I was like, "Oh, that's" and
I've passed I've sent around to a bunch
of people. It's kind of like an
overwhelming thought maybe so so people
forget I told them. But I'm telling you
now it's happens every as sure as a 33
peeking out from behind the [laughter]
clouds. There's this Oh, and the guy
that figured it out or that looked it
up, his name searched and mine from a
certain Middle Eastern uh Dan Bonino
country uh uh as well as DC. So yeah.
No, they do that. I don't know how they
left that that long. I really I I don't
understand it. But yeah, of course,
these searches are done just before
that. It's probably clean up on the
people's trails and all that kind of
[ __ ] and then nobody bothered to check.
I don't know.
Uh oh, ask about the mooneyies. Did you
have you gotten into mooneyies on your
on your show yet?
>> No. No. Tell me about the mooneyies.
Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> The He's like the uh boy, I didn't give
North Korea enough credit, man. They
don't have like uh South Korea is North
Korea with lights. That's it. And uh
[laughter]
>> you know how they tell you how bad North
Korea is because a satellite will show
you at night it's pitch black and South
Korea's all lit up and those poor North
Koreans are getting healthy natural
sleep the way you're supposed to.
[laughter] Those poor [ __ ]
>> That's a good point. Yeah,
>> I got to sleep with headphones on. I'm
[ __ ] up. Okay, so uh Sunyong Moon, I
think it's a a construct of the Korean
CIA, which is the name of their CIA. Um,
and uh, but the mooneyies are connected
to TP all these TPUSA fake [ __ ]
Christians.
They're directly connected to them. And
you see Nuke Gingrage at these uh,
Mooney events in South Korea and they
look insane. Talk about making fun of
Remember North Korea, everybody violins
uh,
uh, Rage Against the Machine like
perfectly and it's a whole I'm watching
this mother moon ceremony. It's the
craziest thing I've I think I've ever
seen. It's like you're watching a a
space opera knockoff of Star Wars or
something and uh 2004 they crowned Suny
Young Moon the Messiah Congress did it
sounds like I dreamt that but that's a
thing that happened because he gives him
money you know and then his son with the
bullet crown lives in Pennsylvania now
the splinter group but um you know I I
haven't watched the Candace Owens thing
that I think she has brought it up the
trafficking element but the mooneyies
are known for human trafficking and the
president of Japan got shot that time by
a disgruntled guy whose mother had spent
everything on the Mooney. The Mooneyies
infiltrated Japan a while ago, I guess.
>> Right. Right. Yeah.
>> So, whoever that president that liked he
was he was into Elvis or something was
his like little
>> um he had allowed that and this guy made
like a shotgun out of wood or something
like that and shot it,
>> right? And it's because of that. And
apparently a bunch of Japanese really
sympathized with this guy because the
mooneyies are a problem in there.
>> It's probably like another Jesuit
invasion to them, you know?
>> Right.
>> It's all the same thing. They all do the
same thing.
>> It's all the same thing. [laughter]
>> It's all blood sacrifice and pretending
to be a thing that you're not
>> and spy work, which is what magic. I
mean, that's where it comes from is from
like lies and hiding things. And I mean,
that's just what the [ __ ] it is.
>> No. Well, look, look, the easiest way to
infiltrate and subvert a country is
through these cults, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Because these cults engage in all sorts
of like, you know, sexual blackmail,
ritual sacrifice. I mean, they
compromise everyone. They have they have
this vast network that's that's covert.
So, yeah, I mean, like the easiest way
if you want to um subvert a country is
you just compromise and um um subvert
the the secret societies. Um, apathiosis
69. Let him talk. Hey, Professor Jen, I
I I like you talking. I don't know why
he's young.
>> No, no, I love you talking as well. I
mean, I came here to learn, right?
>> I don't know why you think Professor Jen
shouldn't talk so much. He's the guest.
You sound like a fool.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. You know, I watch your show all
the time, so I know exactly what to
expect on your show. So,
>> a good interview show in the least, and
I just want to meet people on the show.
>> It's not meant to be a conversation,
man. It's not meant to be a
conversation. No.
>> Uh, I love you guys. See Ted Cruz say
stop attacking PDFs. Okay. Did he
literally say that? Because
>> he did say that. Yes.
>> What do you mean like in prisons or what
is it? What does
>> that interview? Yeah, he did say he he
he said two things recently that that
that got a lot of attention. He said
this, but he also said um about how you
know Israel is this mezanic state that
we should all worship as Christians.
Well, we if you bless God blesses those
He doesn't know the scripture, but God
blesses those who bless Israel. And look
at all the blessings we've been
receiving clearly. Do the blessings ever
stop? I don't spoil us, Ted, with
blessings.
>> Yeah. Do you know Michael Tracy?
>> Yeah.
>> Do you Okay. He's been saying this as
well where he's he's been saying like,
you know, like, you know, 14 year olds
are tenderly not pedophiles. You know,
>> my girlfriend not a pedophile. I watched
him doing it and my girlfriend says so
I'm like so someone's paying him I guess
he's trying to get those bounties they
do for you but she's like no that he's
into that he's defending himself
[laughter] she says that watch it now I
don't know but it he's like a very small
oily man and I just can't imagine you'd
want to pay but this is before I knew
about that bounty system they do where
like if you say the right things you can
collect like 50k so it could be that you
know it just he does look like a guy
that
My Little Pony appreciate her a little
bit. I mean, let's not Okay.
>> Well, I mean, like, but like what's
funny is like he says this, but he's
also very passionate about it. He's
almost like a crusade to convince people
14 year olds are not children. and they,
you know, in most countries they're they
can marry, you know, and
>> yeah, you sign a permission slip from,
by the way, in America and a lot of
states, I think not all the states, I
hope, but a bunch of them because
especially the Mormy ones, uh, they're
letting 14-year-old marriages. I I I I
would hope it's changed by now, but I
don't look into that stuff because I'm
not a prevert. Okay, let's see.
Professor Jen, can you talk more about
the AI future model you described in
your interview with RT? Thank you for
sharing your work with us. Uh what was
that what you were talking about before?
>> Uh AI future model. Okay. So I was
talking about the idea of Pax Judea,
>> right? Where Jerusalem is a capital of
the world
>> and how the system would run is um
through AI. So you have these three uh
nations that are heavily invested in AI.
There are United States, Israel and
China. And as we discussed, if you look
behind the curtain, you'll you you'll
see that it's the same people behind all
the development of AI in all three
nations, right? So what this means is
that um if all three nations succeed in
creating AI, they'll use this AI to
create the surveillance state. So
digital currency, digital um ID. So
China's pretty far ahead in that. Um
Israel is probably the most
sophisticated. America is trying to
catch up. But like, you know, if you're
able to control the AI infrastructure
beyond all three, then then you
basically control all three nations
through through artificial intelligence.
And and that's a game plan behind Pax
Judea, if that makes any sense.
>> Is Europe [snorts] what what is Europe's
plan with that?
>> Well, Europe destroyed, man. Have you
been following the news in in in Europe?
The intention is to destroy Europe. I'm
I'm serious. That's right.
>> Civil war in Britain, civil war in
France. You got this Islamic invasion
going on. I mean I mean the intention is
to crash Europe and then once it's
destroyed then you can build the um AI
state.
>> Venture capital is really consolidating
our various things. Uh it's my belief
that these ice raids are oh uh it's my
belief these from this M thanks. My it
is my belief these ICE raids are a
purposeful social agitation operations
infiltrated with MSAD and CIA just like
the phony Patriot front. Yeah, I I
believe that.
>> I agree. Yeah. Yeah. No, I I it seems
too coordinated. It seems too
intentional. I mean like I mean again
they have all this um social science um
data from studying uh Facebook, from
studying Iraq, Afghanistan. So like they
know exactly what they're doing. They
know exactly how to warp people's
emotions to create as much violence as
possible.
>> Um yeah, I mean it hey works. Uh yo Kurt
I grew up watching Ugly Americans on
Comedy Central. Uh, you got me hooked
last year. My awakening with the Tracy
Twim. Oh, yeah. Tracy Twimman stuff is
like wild, dude. That's uh, she really
figured out all that Tempo [ __ ] better
than anybody I've ever seen. Uh, Game
Boy 3232. The idea of mystery schools
always makes me think of this Spongebob
episode called The Secret Box, where
Patrick withholds information from
Spongebob with a secret box and the word
Enigma comes up, too. Oh, yeah. They're
making fun of that. Spongebob was a
funny show for a funny kid show of its
time. But yeah, that's clearly what that
is,
>> right? So mystery schools, right? If you
go back in history, mystery schools were
just an opportunity for the elite to
indulge their sexual deprivity and feel
good about themselves while doing it.
>> Well, it's m that's the drill. That's
the real magic.
>> That's [laughter] that's real magic
>> is feeling good after.
Okay. Stank Jesus. Candace Owens has
been talking about the experiments with
gay kids in Project Looking Glass. Her
comments yesterday are full of gay kids.
Yeah, I bet. Uh and and uh look, when
she's telling the truth about Now, look,
here's two questionable things not
related to this this TPUSA, which I I
haven't seen anything that I'm like, oh,
how could you say that, Candace? Sounds
like she's on on the ball. So, that's
good. But it was very strange to defend
Danny Masterson from Scientology, which
she did. And it's very strange to think
with Harvey Weinstein is the real victim
because balls are sewn up in his legs.
And I take the way I took that was
that's John Mappen, the Scientologist
billionaire. Everybody's got a
billionaire, dude. If you if you want to
have a platform, you got a billionaire
who's going to allow you to say
whatever. And some of them are going to
allow you to say some [ __ ] It's like a
nice feudal times like always. And so
that's why if all these gate kids are
commenting,
uh I I hope it ain't like one of them
Reddit uh sting operations to draw
people in to talk about things that
happened to them and then you don't hear
from them no more and there's a lot of
sudden hangings
or something uh you know Omega Omega's
out. Uh C can Kurt with a guest shout
out Sumo dog. It's a real dog named Sumo
Bear. It's SE's dog and SW is a comedy.
Oh, so a guy named Squeeze.
Okay. Uh, sumo dog. Uh, wait.
So, you want me to shout sumo bear or a
sumo dog? I've never heard of a sumo
dog. Have you?
Um, you got to send me a picture or
something, but I I'll say shout out to
your friend's dog, just in case that has
anything to do with something I don't
want to shout out. Okay. Uh, Chris,
because I don't know who the [ __ ]
Squeeze is. Uh Chris 5454, please ask if
Chinese learn about plasma in science
class. Your inverted plasma ball is 100
years behind current electrical
engineering, but it matches up with the
electron gas model in physics. Oh, you
know anything about this?
>> Look, I don't know about this
specifically, but I will tell you that
science education in China is terrible
because it's all theoretical knowledge.
So, you just memorize formulas and you
memorize uh information from books, but
you actually don't you actually don't
engage in um experiments. you actually
don't actually see how things work in in
real life. Um, and that's why, you know,
Chinese are good at good at test, but if
you actually ask them to build
something, it might blow up on you.
>> Um, how's that Montreal? cuz I still
when I took it it was good. But I had
heard a story about um it collapsing in
one province like years before when the
other guy before pay and uh and they
like put it into a ditch and people were
in it,
>> right? Yeah. So
>> you got executed or something that was
official. That's what I was told.
>> Yeah. So, um, in China, um, if something
happens, you're incentivized to cover it
up because, um, you know, if it becomes
a big deal, then you get fired as an
official and your family loses all its
wealth and privilege, right? So, um,
they're encouraged to cover it up. Uh,
but but, uh, what you're referring to is
um, when they first had the highspeed
rail and they really couldn't they
really didn't understand the limits of
it. So it went too fast and it went too
fast and then it derailed and about
2,000 people died. Um but but but now
they're much better at at that. So
highsp speeded rail is actually a pretty
impressive achievement in China. The
problem though is that it's is
essentially a white elephant meaning
that it's it's more expensive to
maintain highspeed rail than um it is is
then you can actually generate uh
profits from selling customers uh from
sell tickets to customers. So, so
eventually you're you're going to reach
a point where they can't maintain
anymore and it's going to fall apart.
[snorts]
>> It's like uh she's saying it's like uh
like maintaining our militaries.
[laughter]
>> Yeah. Basically, basically trillion.
>> Yeah. Trump went from 1 trillion to 1.5
trillion. And what people understand is
that it doesn't mean a more effective
military. It just means more corruption
and grab.
>> Yeah. Well, that's so so the stupid
boutique right and boutique left. The on
the right they'll they don't get that
and then on the left they think like oh
well taxes and you're like if you're
stealing the taxes then it doesn't [ __ ]
only works if everybody's not stealing
everything which they are. So I mean
it's so stupid to argue about political
theory when everyone is a goddamn
criminal running you and they're just
going to do crimes. You got to clean
them out which Trump should have done
day one. He kind of implied he was going
to Steve Bannon should pushed it. So, so
Evan's attention is on like this double
force raid that captured Maduro, right?
Who is who I think is a CIA asset, by
the way? But like
>> why?
>> Well, I mean, how else could you have
captured him? I mean, he he needed to
have cooperated with you, right? Um,
>> wait, wait. I thought his wife Wait,
wait. I thought the VP was rad. Well,
here's what I thought. That VP was
working with us, CIA, and he
[clears throat] cuz they were hitting
them with uh energy weapons. They're
like, "No, shit."
>> That That's just misinformation. Come up
with the fact cover up with the fact
that Maduro is a CI asset. And and
>> and here's how we'll know. Okay. During
the trial, during the trial, Maduro will
say that Venezuela participated in the
stealing of the 2020 election
>> using Yes. Yes. Watch that. Watch that.
>> Wow. That's a good I wouldn't have never
seen that. That's a real twist.
>> Yeah. The the smartmatic machines,
right? They use investable as well. and
and Maduro is gonna say that uh
Venezuela participated in the still 2020
elections and he'll get a pardon for
this. So it's all soul trial.
>> Uh well I mean it's not not believable
just I didn't see that coming at all. Um
yeah very interesting. So, so, so, so,
no, I was going to point out that, you
know, it see like the American military
seems very impressive, but then you you
look at Operation Prosperity Guardian,
right? When the the entire American the
Operation Prosperity Guardian was, you
know, when the Houthies were blocking
the the Red Sea, [laughter]
>> right?
>> And the American Navy, okay, you saw the
footage, right? The entire immigrant
Navy went to go blow up the Hi, the
hoofies and they failed. It was a
complete disaster.
>> Yeah. Well, it I mean the best we
haven't won a war in 80 years, but I
mean how do you spend all this money to
never win again? How does that work if
it's not a SK?
>> It was a hilarious thing because you
have to American Navy with all like, you
know, they're destroyers. You have the
General Ford, which is super carrier.
The Houthies had like, you know, like
fishing boats and they couldn't beat the
Houthies.
>> Yeah. Well, uh uh uh you know, the
Houthies have been fighting for years
dealing with this. Like they're the
official government. They're not an
insurgent force. That's the elected
government is them. Alansar or
something. I don't know. Ansara law or
some [ __ ] Um okay. Wait. This is I just
saw this. Uh Booker and Vivc are members
of Yale Shabtai Society. What is that?
The like the Frankest kind of [ __ ] Do
you know anything about this? The Yale
Shabtai Society.
>> I I have no idea what you're talking
about. Booker didn't go to Yale, right?
Booker. Booker. Booker. Uh uh Ko Boker,
right? Koi Boker.
>> Well, is it a I never heard of that
society. Or is he calling it another
society that
um or did he misspell it? We'll find
out.
>> Is it Sabatai? I mean like are you sat
>> Yeah, I assume that means Shab Thai
Zebi, but is it are you saying it as an
insult or do you mean there's an actual
Sha? That's a very strange society to
have.
>> I I've never heard of this.
>> Oh god. [laughter]
>> My god.
>> Oh dear Lord.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, why are so many Indians in these um
why are so many Indians in this stuff?
That doesn't make any sense to me. The
Indian Israel thing. Like why is there
such a connection like that?
>> Oh wow.
>> Yeah, that's wild dude.
Like Yel's famous secret society is Sha
Tisley. Okay, I see where this is going.
[laughter]
Yeah,
we had Vivic Pastrami on uh Jimmy's show
and he was going on about the [ __ ]
Weaggguers and um you notice nobody
talks about weaggguers no more. They
suddenly don't give a [ __ ] They're the
m the only Muslims we ever cared about
supposedly that they don't bring up. But
I go, "How many weaguers are in those
things?" He goes, "A million." I go,
"Well, there's two million in Gaza."
>> Look, look, look. You know, weaggguers
in China were getting along fine. Then
they then, you know, this war on terror
happens, right? And then ISIS comes into
being and ISIS you know they conduct all
this like MK ultra crap on on people and
then suddenly you have like these
terrorist attacks conducted by weagers
who come back from the Middle East in
China now and now now you know it
becomes a problem.
>> So Guantanamo is still open is first of
all we're friends with the leader of
al-Qaeda who runs Syria now.
>> Do people in Guantanamo know that that
we're friends with al Qaeda? Do they get
out or what what goes on in there? I
wonder.
>> Um let's see. Uh,
>> oh, maybe that's all of them. No. Oh,
here we go. Oh, Michelovian. Oh, here.
I'll give you a Michelov. So, tell us
all about the AI future, Professor Jang.
I'm being Jeffrey Michionlo. Somebody
asked. Uh,
>> okay.
>> I wasn't trying to be uh Oh, I didn't
read his thing, though.
Uh, I wasn't trying to be dismissive.
I'm looking into sight as to why you
obviously chose to teach game theory, as
you have for a reason. Thank you. Um,
who's teaching game theory? Me or
>> I'm teaching game theory this semester.
Last semester I taught secret societies.
This theory this this semester I'm
teaching game theory. Um, and okay,
>> tell us about game theory.
>> Yeah. So, so, so here's my grand plan.
Okay. My plan eventually is start my own
religion. And so I'm using this YouTube
platform in order to test certain um
ideas that I will I will need for for
for this new religion. And that's why I
switch around a lot. So, so you know if
you're a fan of certain topic uh you can
get annoyed because then like you know
like next semester I'll teach something
completely different. But but again my
my my goal is to be the Messiah. My my
goal is [laughter]
point.
>> So so so I'm going through the R&D phase
of my life right now.
>> Yeah. This is you can do uh travel to
Gnostic uh India as the you could have
like a Japanese brother whatever the
[ __ ] they say Christ did in Gnostic with
the internet now.
>> Yeah. No, no. I mean like like I will
eventually go these places but like like
at this point I'm I'm just trying to um
innovate with the um framework. Um and
then eventually I'll go and spread my
message like Paul did. Um you know I'll
travel like like Paul the the apostle.
[snorts]
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I'm familiar. Uh uh
let's see. I like history. This is from
Vic Victor Nation. I liked history. I
never got what we were taught to hate
Russian China when they helped us during
World War II. They were allies and I'm
an ex uh Jehovah Witness. Brother Ker, I
think because of communism, but then it
didn't make sense after nobody really
does communism now. Uh said ner
century. Yeah, I'm Zionist. Whatever.
[laughter]
I'm also into Cabala and drinking
tequila all night. Well, thanks for the
50 [laughter] bucks.
Sounds like if you like Pina Colada's
song.
Uh, ask me if Losher Nostra has
influence in China. Does it? I I feel
like it doesn't. Uh, uh, or there's not
like Is there a MSAD China ops that you
I've ever heard of?
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Israel is huge in China.
Israel does a lot of business in China.
You have a lot of Israelis um in in in
China. Look, China and Israel are best
friends. People don't really
>> I don't see them fight ever. I've never
heard of that.
>> Um
yeah, I mean um like like look look you
you remember the Hespella the Hesper
attacks,
>> right? When when Israel just blew up
these pagers and it castrated a lot of
people.
>> Yeah. Blew his girl's face off a little
kid. Yeah.
>> What that tells us and like no one
talked about this, right? What it tells
us is basically that the Israelis
control the global supply chain and you
can't do that without the help of chi
Chinese manufacturers. Right. So so
>> interesting.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh right, right right.
>> Yeah. I see. I never think in supply
chains because I'm uh trash. Uh okay.
Hemorrhoid herd says, "I went to Promise
Girl excursion to an outback mining town
in 76. They let us kids play on a
massive yellow cake pile.
>> [laughter]
>> Is that really?
>> Yeah.
>> Go take a dinkery doo on top of this.
Uh, let's see. Time traveling
philanthropist Kurt. Do you think the
reason wizards put their disgusting
sigil acts in our faces is because they
need our permission, but they're trying
to absolve themselves. Yeah, that's the
revelation of the method. That's a
thing. Uh, is it Michael Hoffman? I just
gave his book to Duncan to read the
Twilight language. But yeah, that it's
just the iPhone agreement.
South Park summed it up in that iPhone
episode where they they made him into a
human scent pad. Uh, tons of K and C
tons of KFC connections in Austin comedy
scene. What's KFC?
>> Knights of Columbus.
>> Ew, really? I didn't know that. Dude,
you know about Knights of Columbus?
>> Yeah, there's a big Knights of Columbus
building in New Haven where Yale is. And
um a lot of people think it's just a
continuation of Templars, but there
there's like a distinct version.
>> They're to kill they're they're out to
get freemason. Well, they I don't know
now that they are, but they were
designed and all their vows are I will
kill the Protestant and smash their baby
and the rocks and all those stupid vows.
>> All those Jack the Ripper vows you got
to take.
>> And uh but that real big boy traffickers
though, that's the thing they're real
into. Lake Havisu who watch Nathan
Reynolds thing. That's his grandpa was a
programmer with the Knights of Columbus
and he got
>> historically historically the Catholic
Church has been very anti- Freemasonic.
So I think the Knights of Columbus is
like uh Freemasonry for Catholics
essentially.
>> Um yeah. Well, but I think they're all I
don't think none of these names matter
really anymore like that. And and I
think at the end of the day, they're all
just to gather together people that are
from the right heritage.
>> And uh and all the other allegorories
and all that, you know, like if you're
useful, you'll be used, but if you're
not, then you could sit and try to
figure out what what the two pillars of
Well, King Boaz mean all goddamn day.
Like a jerk off, like an ancient pharaoh
memorizing horseshit [laughter] with
your life.
Uh let's see. Comedy and dope by Kigley.
Big Jay is live now. Uh, conspiracy
people uh don't know loans create
deposits. Uh, what does that mean? Loans
create deposits.
I guess you got me there, dude. Uh,
>> wait, wait, wait, sorry, sorry, sorry. I
I think what what he meant is um the
fractional reserve system where if you
you know, if a bank loans you a billion
dollars,
>> it's actually considered an asset, not a
a liability. It's like
>> that that's that's what he's referring
to. Sorry. [snorts]
>> Oh, wow. You totally stumped the old
curb here. Uh, love both of your content
channels. So true. Both sides is are
stealing and corrupted. Trump torpedoing
CIA ops in Venezuela to rail them in.
Whoever them and they are.
Oh, okay. So, what? There was a CIA
thing going on in Venezuela and that's
why he did that. Is that the idea of
bringing that I guess Maduro,
the Jewish CIA agent who hates Israel? I
don't. But it's gets real wacky, dude.
Just like uh Mcronone's wife having a
dick is the least of it. Uh let's see.
Barry, I was in small schools, 160 kids
in rural Illinois and gifted 1995. I
know knew at least two out of 12 of us
had job apps for CIA right out of high
school. Oh, so you were probably in a
good uh I mean not good but a gate
program where they were, you know,
looking for uh I I don't know if I was
in one that went because there's so many
private contractors doing that and I but
I don't remember it either. So uh let's
see. K Samsung is selling with Israel
hardware inside their phone. Who's to
say they aren't selling them? And they
are. But don't worry, all of our [ __ ]
has already been set up by Israel. Our
whole don't worry about that.
Exactly.
>> Don't Don't worry about Jews owning the
media. Je one one guy Jew owns the
media. [laughter]
Larry Ellison
uh bring back Goolags says, "What is up
with Shen Yun?" I don't know who Shen
Yun.
>> Do you know Shenyun?
>> That's like the dance, you know, the
dance thing they do. It's like a Chinese
cultural uh theater.
>> The ones that look like goth, but it's
like dance music they're into. Well,
they dress up in like the traditional
Chinese outfits and they do a whole like
play about traditional Chinese culture.
I think the idea is that the um
>> Oh, wait, wait, wait.
>> The group of people that are
>> the Fallon thing,
>> China. Yeah. They they put this on every
year to portray communist culture or
Chinese culture before communism.
Basically, it's the
>> fallen gong is, I was told, maybe you
know or don't know, Professor Jen, uh
it's it's Asian Scientology. It's just
Scientology for Asia. That's what fallen
gong is. Have you ever heard anything
like that?
>> Yeah. No. Um um I mean Fall & Gong was a
huge thing back in the 1990s. Um and
it's um CIA adjacent of course like all
all these religions. And we know this
because the founder of the Falong
Liongjur, he went to uh New York. He
lives there now. He set up a media
empire. Um
>> yeah. So like how would how how would he
be able to do that, right? So so so I
think it's CIA adjacent. [snorts]
>> Yeah, it's got to be. I you can't just
set up a media empire [laughter] just
move to a new country even one our [ __ ]
as much as
>> it's influential. It's influential like
Epic Times. I mean it's pretty
influential United States.
>> Well, I've seen them do good reporting.
I mean Christian Science Monitor has
done good reporting even though it's
like related to Christian Science which
is kind of stupid as her thing,
>> right? you know, it's just what are they
going to not report about? And uh they
don't want to have to tell you what to
not report about. You're supposed to
just kind of know. They want uh uh uh
what do you call it? Um
pre uh uh like compliance, anticipatory
compliance. They want to train you
rather than us having to tell you rules
because we might want to change them.
What's really funny is like these um
these Chinese groups, dissident groups
in America, they're all right-wing. They
they all they think it's Messiah. Um you
know, it's Yeah.
>> Have you heard of um when I was there,
they were telling me that cuz sometimes
there'll be like missionaries and [ __ ]
in China that or just religious people
and because it's and I saw this, it
wasn't religious when I was there at
all. They they weren't down they weren't
into like religion jokes or like sex
jokes. They were kind of uptight. I
wouldn't say uptight, just not they
don't weren't interested in hearing
that. They want to hear race stuff a lot
people said. But he said people go crazy
because it's so bereft of anyone that
believes in any kind of religion that
people get like um they'll they'll start
like a bird lands on their window and
they'll be like it's a sign from God
because they start to lose it. It's so
isolating that no one else is uh in
which uh I don't know if you ever heard
of that but it sounds very interesting.
Look, look, look. I mean, like, what's
really interesting is that China is the
most atheist country in the world. It's
most most materialistic, but like you
look at any Chinese organization. It's
set set up as a cult. It's not set up
like as as like religious cult. And like
you just look look at the things that
that that they do. Um and you and you
look at the people who these
entrepreneurs, they're all like messiah
figures like like Jack Ma like I mean
just look at his behavior and he's like
this guy is like if you didn't know he's
entrepreneur you would think that this
guy was leader of this evil cult in
China.
>> When he does those big uh Alibaba
rallies, you know, it's kind of like
doing the Apple one, but he has like
this ponytail. He's doing like Michael
Jackson dances and [ __ ] And uh
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Then he went away for
a couple months and he shut his trap
after that. I mean, don't make me love
you, China, grabbing your billionaires
and making them shut their mouths.
>> But, but I mean, the issue is that
they're all like that. I mean, like,
like, you know, Jack M successful, but
like they're all like that. If you run a
company in China, you don't see yourself
as an entrepreneur entrepreneur. You see
yourself as this religious figure that
um inspires your your people. And and
like, you know, it goes back to the time
of the culture revolution when Maudon
was like that. like Maong was not a
leader of a nation. He was like, you
know, the founder of a religion. I mean,
he he I mean, he was considered a
methodic figure in China.
>> That's why I follow Jake Paul
unquestioningly. [laughter]
I invest in any crypto coin he invents.
And uh we have that that's what our
influencers are. Like all of our
influencers are that they're all setting
up a cult of personality.
>> That's that's the zoo big sell you a
memecoin and then rip you off.
>> Yeah. Repeatedly.
Oh, you know who Jake Paul is? The dude
from uh
>> Yeah.
>> He he has uh him and his brother Logan.
He does he was boxing. He just got beat
up by some gay guy recently.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And and like like like why
is it like whoever fights them like
loses a limb or loses his life
afterwards.
>> So I thought a friend of the guys got
killed when he went back to Nigeria or
something. They something blew up and a
he didn't die but a friend was killed.
>> Yeah. But if you look at his the history
of people who engage in fights with with
um Jake Paul and who lo who like defeat
him, bad things happened to them
afterwards. I mean like it's it's
>> they probably breached the contract by
him losing. I mean the whole idea all
these fighters have been saying they're
doing fixed fight. The Mike Dyson fight
obviously was Mike D is biting his
gloves during the fight to remind him
not to punch Jake Paul because he just
needs to make this 80 million to fix his
knees or whatever the [ __ ] wrong with
him. Like You know, and uh Jake Paul got
[ __ ] up. He got his face [ __ ] up by
that guy.
>> Yeah.
>> Um and so, you know, you already know
they got holes in their brain. I mean,
they've done on their own shows got
their brain diagrams and they got those
psychopath holes in their brain. [ __ ]
They're probably Monarch who at the end
of He was a Disney kid. Disney people
are [ __ ] He's one of the more successful
ones of Disney kids and he's [ __ ] up.
It's real gross, dude. I'm still waiting
to get into that Club 33 in Disney
though. I hear that's very exclusive. Do
you know about that?
>> No. No. No.
>> There's like a club you can join in
Disneyland or Disney World, an exclusive
club called Club 33.
>> Yeah.
>> And how do you get in?
>> Oh, it takes years, you know, cuz they
these amusement parks for some reason
have like I don't know if it's not
exactly. It's very close to Vatican
status where they're their own governed.
Oh, and uh Walt Disney Epcot was
supposed to be the first 15-minute city.
That was Walt Disney's Dream Nightmare,
>> which uh I didn't know until Andy Hunt
played that. Yeah. No, this has been in
the works a while, dude. We're It's
gonna be a uh you know, and I for one
welcome our uh the No.
>> So So you know, you you said this, but
if you want to see America's future,
just come to China and and and spend
spend a couple weeks. Okay.
>> I mean, I mean, as a joke, I used to say
it and it was true, though.
>> It was true. Oh, wow. Oh, I'm out of
time. Holy [ __ ] I got to do a show.
Hey, thanks for coming on short notice,
Professor Joe. I really appreciate it.
Uh
>> yeah. No, I'm a huge fan of the show. I
mean like it was it's so much fun to
hang out. So
>> yeah, that uh that CIA Maduro thing is
very interesting. You
>> watch what happens. Watch what
>> I will. I will. All right. Well, that's
our show everybody. He just got derp.